eyefootball.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy | eyefootball.com

By using eyefootball.com you agree to us collecting and using your personal information in accordance with the following details.

We are committed to your right to privacy and will only use your data as set out below.  
This privacy policy has been created specifically for football news site www.eyefootball.com. Please read this information carefully. By using eyefootball.com you agree to us collecting and using your personal information in accordance with the following details.

### Compliance with legislation

We operate and are registered in accordance with all applicable data protection legislation in England and Wales.

### Collection of data

We may collect data about you, some of which could be personal, in a variety of ways, including:

1\. when you register with the website;  
2\. when you purchase products or services from the site or from any of our other platforms;   
3\. when you enter competitions and/or complete surveys; and   
4\. through the use of certain data capturing devices (for example studying which pages you read the most through the use of cookies).

### Contacting you

eyefootball.com will send sometimes send e-mails to the e-mail address you have given us. We will not accept responsibility if anyone else gets hold of your e-mails. If you send us an e-mail, you cannot assume that it has reached us until we return an e-mail acknowledging receipt. Please note that the internet is not a completely secure medium. Please advise us if you experience any issues at all.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Whenever you visit our website (unless you elect not to receive cookies), then your computer will store an identifying code in the cookie. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. 

We use cookies to help us (i) estimate and report our total audience size and traffic (ii) conduct research to improve our content and services (iii) to make your user experience more simple in a variety of different ways, for example you do not need to type in your user name each time you return to the site. 

Please note that we allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not our Privacy Policy. 

### Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Website are delivered to you, on our behalf, by our web advertising partner. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads. 

### Amendments to this Policy

We may amend this policy from time to time however we assure you that we only use your data and for our legitimate business reasons and in order to give you a better user experience. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our homepage.
